Rachlin, Marge Oral History Interview with Lawrence Rogin 5689 OH
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Marge Rachlin Oral History Interview with Lawrence Rogin
1981
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rogin, Lawrence
Rachlin, Marge
5689 OH
2.83 cubic feet
2.3 linear ft.
Oral histories (document genre).
Audio tapes of oral history interviews.
3338530
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 01, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 27, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5766 OHM: Lawrence Rogin Interview Master Tapes 5766 OHT: Lawrence Rogin Interview Transcripts 5691 OH: Lawrence Rogin Interview on the CSEA-AFSCME Merger
Labor unions -- United States; Trade-union leadership. Interviews.; Oral histories.; Rogin, Lawrence, 1909-1988; Rachlin, Marge
3338530
- Interview with Larry Rogin - Nov. 3 & 5, 1980 (1) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  transcript
- Interview with Larry Rogin - Nov. 3 & 5, 1980 (2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Interview with Larry Rogin - Nov. 3 & 5, 1980 (corrected copy) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Interview with Larry Rogin - Nov. 3 & 5, 1980 (corrected copy) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Larry's original outline (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Tape 1 & 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Transcript
- Original - tape 3 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Original - tape 4 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Original - tape 5 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Original - tape 6 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Original - tape 7 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Original - tape 8 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Original - tape 9 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Original - tape 10 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Original - tape 11 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Original - tape 12 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Original - tape 13 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Original - tape 14 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Rogin - Nov. 3, 1980 - tape 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  side 1-2
- Rogin - Nov. 3, 1980 - tape 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  side 3-4
- Rogin - Nov. 3, 1980 - tape 3 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  side 4-5
- Tape 4 - 1/27/1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  side 5-6
- Tape 5 - 1/27/1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  side 8-9
- Tape 6 - May 6, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Tape 7 - May 5, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Tape 8 - May 6, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Tape 9 - 5/12/1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Tape 10 - May 12, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Tape 11 -May 27, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Tape 12 - May 27 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Tape 13 - 6/8/1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Tape 14 - Aug. 4, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Tape 15 - 8/4/1981: AFL-CIO, Southern Staff Time work w/universities (Box 18, Folder 1)